FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
FORGET WHAT I SAID
It's May...
The season where greenery
begins to shine brightly.
You know, I always assumed... At least out
of all the other guys in class, I was the
one who was by far the closest
with you. But maybe I was wrong?
I wonder what he meant when he said that.
And also how was I
supposed to respond to it...
I can't stop thinking about it.
K-Kazehaya said that out of kindness to
me, but then I got anxious, and became
self-conscious and acted all awkward...
Ugh, I can't believe I was so rude!
Yeah, I was so pissed I
decided to go home by myself.
I don't blame you. I
would've done the same thing.
Hm?
And then, the second I
left I got a text right away.
Does... everything I do creep people out?
I want to go back to how things were
before... when I could talk to Kazehaya
naturally without freaking out. but now...
I can't remember... how I ever managed that
in the first place.
Hey! Hey, Kazehaya! So what do you
wanna do over the lunch break today?
Let's play soccer outside
since the weather's nice.
I can finally show off
my super awesome kick!
Well, I guess I'm not
surprised they're playin' again...
Nakai, Negishi, you
guys wanna join us too?
- You sure?
- You're both on the soccer team, you
gotta be good. Maybe you could show us a
few new tricks?
Sure! No problem! All right!
Morning, Kuronuma.
Be friendly. And natural...
G- good... Morning.
Hey, Kazehaya!
Uh-huh?
All he's doing is treating me the way he
treats everyone else... And I'm still acting
- like this.
- Yeah, yeah. That's why
Mr. Prince Charming is so...
Who wouldn't fall for him when he greets
you with a bright smile and then softly
- gazes into your eyes?
- Huh? What th'heck 're
you talking about, Kento?
Good morning Sadako, what's up?
He did it again today!
So friendly and natural!
G...Good morn--
No! C'mon, that's way too rigid!
"Good morning!"
Good morning...
- Don't frown!
- Good morning.
Try it this way. Good morning! Go!
Good mor...
- Good morning!
Kinda intense.
- Well, they're sure getting along.
G'morning!
Huh? What?
It's nothing.
Two people can say they
feel "love" for one another.]
But, with Kazehaya and I... the meaning
behind that word may be totally different.
My stomach hurts...
Actually, I've been
pretty constipated lately.
Aww, that sounds rough.
- Huh? The heck did Sawako go?
- The bathroom?
This helps with constipation.
- A weed?
- What am I supposed to do with that?
- Looks like another new quirk...
- ...To add to the list.
What's up?
Ready?
Did something happen?
You seem kinda depressed lately.
Really?
Mmhm.
All right, next!
We're still getting used to our new
classmates... I should have never said those
things... when I'm sure she
was just trying to blend in.
You got this! I could see on her
face that I was stressing her out.
Who?
Kuronuma.
And when you say "those
things"? What do you mean...
Just don't ask.
So selfish.
You're right. That's just the kind of
person I am. Super selfish, reckless, and
- possessive by nature.
- And short-tempered.
That's why... my patience is at its limit. I
know it'll be hard on her. But I want to
tell her everything.
You were...
Being patient?
It's just... don't want to stress her out.
She's worked so hard to
get to where she is now.
I mean, it seems like she likes
you a lot though, y'know, Shota?
Well, it's not like I think
she hates me or anything, but...
GOT CHOCOLATES FOR SOME REASON →
Kazehaya's such a
cheerful guy! I admire him so!
I respect him too!
That's all there is to it!
How am I cheerful?! Screw that!
Where'd that come from? I never said...
Dude. What's going on, are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
Someone else might already
have their sights set on her.
When I think about other people popping
up who start to like her I can't help it...
It's driving me crazy.
Are we both looking at the same girl here?
To me, she looks like a kokeshi doll.
I don't exactly
understand, but that's really tough.
That makes me feel worse.
Hold up, where you heading off to, Sawako?
Actually, if the two of you aren't too
busy, would you mind coming with me?
Check it out. Welcome to my
little herb corner. Look!
DETOX
HARD ARTERIES INSOMNIA
- What's the deal with these labels?
- I thought if I added those,
they'd be more helpful to everyone!
Uh, w-wait, don't you usually
write the name of the plants?
I thought writing the
therapeutic effects would be easier.
The way you wrote 'em it looks like
they'll cause constipation or diarrhea.
Yeah! They look more
like the labels for curses!
Uhh... what if I add
"therapeutic effects" or "general use"...
Urgh, too small.
"Diuretic use"?
- Kento.
Oh! The two of you called me by
my first name! Ya gotta love that!
I was hoping it was
Kazehaya... I just thought...
You thought I was him, right? Sadako?
You totally thought it
was the guy you like?
You see, I know cause I'm psychic.
Y- You're psychic?
He's so natural, super
friendly... and psychic.
Uh oh, you're tensing
your face again. Chill.
Like I said, 'a girl shouldn't keep their
face muscles all tense like that. You know
I'm basically a philanthropist, so I just
can't ignore girls who seem to be giving
up on their own happiness.
- Like we're supposed to know this?
"Giving up"?
Now, let's see...
If I show you this signal, you smile!
- Was that my imagination just now?!
- She has you as the perfect female role
model so it's a real shame, right? Ayane?
Thanks for that, but step back.
Oh, by the way, you actually
have really nice legs, Yoshida.
So, m'I right Sadako?
Aw man, guess that smile just
isn't checking the boxes, huh?
Come on, it's clearly too much
for her, stop trying to force it.
Yeah. It's scary.
I- I, uh...
I'd really like to be
more natural. Please Master.
Master? What?
A Master, eh? I think I
could get on board with that.
And I will try my best, Master Psychic!
Don't frown! And let's keep the
"master" and "psychic" separate there...
- What is this guy's end game?
- Yes, my psychic master!
Kento!
- Long time no see!
- How's your new class been treating you?
- And are there any cute girls?
- I don't know if I'd say cute, but
there is a girl I'm interested in.
- What's she like?
- A tense, gloomy girl.
The heck does that mean?
- What are you up to?
- Ohh, Ayane.
You've been plotting
something. What is it?
Woah, plotting? You think that? But why?
Because for some reason you just
won't stop messing with Sawako.
Ah. Well it's because Sadako
has a crush on Kazehaya right?
I knew it.
H-Hold on, don't stick your nose where it
doesn't belong. This is an important time
- for her.
- Oh, is it now?
Don't worry about it, I'm
one of the good guys, okay?
See ya.
How could I... not worry?
This here will be on your midterms!
Ugh, it's already midterms?
Time flies, huh?
Oh, by the way, during first year,
wasn't there some cursed notebook from
Sadako being passed around Class D?
Yeah, but it wasn't cursed. In fact,
the class's average shot up because of it.
- Seriously?!
- It sure did.
Huh?
During the midterms last
year, Sadako's cursed notes...
A curse to raise scores...
- No, no! The one that brings fortune...
- Pay attention this'll
probably be on there too!
- Huh? What are they talking about?
- The notes Sadako put together were a real
life-saver during the midterms last year.
- So you're accomplished then!
-"Accomplished"!
This will be on the midterms so...
Hey everyone! After school today, Sadako
says she'll be doing a midterm lecture for
us!
A- A lecture?!
That's a pretty big deal... I'm doing that?!
'Kay? You good with that, Sadako?
- We're in still the middle of class...
- I- I uh...
If... you don't mind me doing it. At the
very least, I have 3 ghost stories ready
to go.
Will I ever live up
to their expectations?
Well, I don't think they'll be
expecting anything like that.
Wow, four people are here!
- That's one way to look at it...
- A lecture will really
- help. This is great.
- Uh-huh!
Yeah, so where the heck's the guy
who suggested this whole thing?
Uh... did it start already?
No, it didn't, but it's just about to.
Awesome, I made it.
Kazehaya ended up coming.
We're here too!
- We just finished cleaning!
- We appreciate it, Sadako!
- MNS: W-Welcome. The pleasure's all mine.
- Did it start?
Takahashi!
I just heard about it from Kazehaya.
- Where's Ryu?
- Aw he's at practice.
- He invited them?
- Gotcha.
- Everybody's here!
- Yeah, we all came!
Hey, Sadako.
- Is it okay if you do math first?
- I'll try my best. Even though... I'm
not sure if I'll be much help. Sure!
There's actually kind
of a crowd in there.
Ah, probably because Kazehaya
told a bunch of people about it.
Mr. Prince Charming?
Apparently, from what I've
heard he can't ignore outcasts.
So that's why.
- Tsuru, you're gonna stay too, right?
- Um, first of all, for this section,
- you'll need to remember this formula...
- Huh? Which one?
I can't see!
I have an idea. Why don't you
use the blackboard up front?
What?! Th-The black...
Oh, totally plus it'll
make taking notes easier!
- Come on, just get up there.
- Okay...
AREA OF THE TRIANGLE
AREA OF ABC IS S, AB=C, BC=A, CA=
I... I got it.
The answer's... -Five times the square
root of two! -Five times the square root
of two!
- The two idiots got it correct!
- 'Cause she made it easy to understand!
Seriously amazing, Sadako!
Isn't this where you show us a smile?
I've never seen her smile!
I didn't know she could do that!
- When Sadako smiles, she brings good luck!
- Well, I've actually seen it before, so!
Yeah, yeah, well I got
to see it loads of times!
Not a contest.
Man, what a sight to see!
- And we solved all the problems too!
- I'm glad I decided to
come for the lecture!
See ya!
- Thanks so much, Sadako!
- Teach us again, okay?
Thank you!
No-No problem thank you
for coming! Th-Thank you!
Sadako! For someone who
struggles with this stuff, you did great!
Master, thanks for everything today!
I wouldn't, I don't think I
would turn her down if she asked me.
"Wood ant"?
- Sorry, mind heading home without me?
- Huh?
I got some business to take
care of. It's kind of important.
Kuronuma.
Do you have a sec?
So, Sawako, we gotta head out now.
Remember? You said you wanted to
check out some dresses together?
Oh, yeah, that's right! We
should get going then, see ya Sawako!
Today I'm going to try... to be warmer...
I'll start with a friendly thank you.
- So...
- U-Um...
- I interrupted him!
- All good. You go first.
Y-you sure? I'm so sorry about that.
I-I just want to say...
I a-appreciate what you did for me today.
I meant for that to be way more natural...
but I'm not good at this. Even though I
was so happy...
I... I don't think I'm very good at...
speaking in front of people, but still,
- I--
- I think you are.
Teaching other people like that...
I think you're really good at it.
I... don't want to do
anything to make Kazehaya hate me.
Remember... what I told you before?
You don't need to worry about it, 'kay?
Forget what I said.
Yo.
I was waiting for you.
I'm subconsciously self-conscious...
The more I take action, the
more... Next time: "Misunderstood"